--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.cc
影片压制:小鱼  字幕调校:小鱼  招募Q号:76846146
这是你的钥匙
Here's your key.
你好
Hello.
对不起 他们一定是给错钥匙了
My bad. They gave me the wrong key.
你没弄错 是我们没有准时退房
Not your bad. We stay a little long.
我们很快就会离开
We're now leaving soon.
好吧
Okay.
- 搞什么? 有人啊 - 没事的 维多
- What the fuck, guy? - It's okay, Viktor.
他是新房客
He's here for the room.
对
Yeah.
你在度假
You're on vacation.
对
Uh, yeah.
我没来过这里 这个小镇蛮酷的
I've actually never been here before. It's... It's a pretty cool town.
你们从哪里来的?
Where are you guys from?
- 乌克兰 - 酷啊
- Ukraine. - Cool.
他绑架了我 我不知道我们要去哪里
Now that he kidnapped me I don't know where we're gonna end up.
你太风骚了
You're so dirty.
够了 你会把我累坏的
Enough. You're gonna wear me out.
来吧
Come.
跟我们一起喝一杯
Have a drink with us.
只不过是伏特加 别害羞
It's vodka, man. Don't be shy.
(伏特加)
来吧
Come on, man.
对 你知道的 我
Yeah. You know, it's...
事实上我有些啤酒 你们喝啤酒吗?
Well, actually I've got some beer. Do you guys drink beer?
啤酒还是冰的
It's still cold.
啤酒吗?
Beer, huh?
对
Yeah.
(比尔森啤酒)
我喜欢这个家伙
I like this guy.
他真的很懂得玩乐 对吧?
He brings party with him, huh?
来吧
Come.
拿去
There you go.
- 好了 - 现在我们得干杯
- There we go. - We do a cheers now, huh?
没错
Sure.
好吧 我要去冲个澡 然后我们就离开
Okay. I go take shower, then we go.
该死
Oh, shit.
该死 对不起 我不是故意的
Fuck. I'm sorry, man. I didn't mean to...
不 为什么?
No. For what?
没关系 那是人性
Never mind. It's human nature.
- 我会盯着所有会动的东西看 - 对
- I'm looking everything that moves. - Right.
- 好吧 - 她真的很辣 对吧?
- Okay. - She's hot, right?
- 对 她真的很辣 - 没错
- Yeah, she's pretty hot. - Yeah.
对
Yeah.
我们去了一家夜店 女孩很辣
Hey, we were in this club, crazy chicks.
你到那里去一定能泡到辣妹
You go there, you're gonna score.
- 我可以给你夜店名片 - 不
- I have club card for you. - Oh, no.
不 你得到那里去玩一下 联络感情
No, no, no. You're gonna go in there, man. Connection.
安卡 我需要那家夜店的名片
Anka, I need that club's card.
- 等一下 我找不到名片 - 好吧
- Oh, hold on. I lose it. - Okay.
宝贝 我需要夜店名片
Baby, I need the club card.
安卡
Anka!
该死 出什么问题了?
Shit. Something's fucking wrong?
搞什么? 安卡
What the fuck? Anka!
快进来 我们有麻烦了
Hey, get in here! We got a problem, man.
安卡
Anka.
说话 说话
Talk. Talk.
快进来帮忙 快点
Hey, get in here, man. Come on!
我想她是心脏病发作 快回答我
I think she's having a heart attack or something. Talk to me!
你在搞什么? 快进来
What the fuck you doing, man? Get in here!
安卡 回答我
Anka, talk to me.
快点 我们得帮她找医生
Come on, man. We gotta get her to a doctor.
帮帮我 去叫医生
Help me, man. Call a fucking doctor!
快点 搞什么? 帮帮我
Hey! Come on, man! What the fuck? Help me!
快去叫医生 你还站在那里做什么?
Call the fucking doctor! What the fuck you standing there?
你在搞什么? 快进来
What the fuck you doing, man? Get in here!
什么?
What...?
发生了什么事?
What is going on?
安卡
Anka.
对 可以动手了
Yeah, we're good to go.
拿去吧
Here.
帮她擦干 如果她病了 价钱就没那么好了
Keep her dry. If she gets sick, we'll have to discount her.
人 皮 客 栈 3
(机场接驳车)
得了吧
Come on.
拜托等到蜜月再亲热吧
Save that shit for the honeymoon, please.
伴郎来了
Oh, the best man.
既然我是伴郎 事实上我就是最棒的郎
You know, since I am the best man, which clearly I am,
为什么她要跟你结婚?
you know, why is it that she's marrying you?
大一时你有过机会
You had your chance freshman year.
- 到底发生了什么事? - 我不知道
- What ever happened? - I don't know.
因为你是花花公子?
You were a man-whore?
别在她面前提这些事 谢谢你的帮忙
Not in front of her. Thanks for that.
来吧 我们走
Come on, let's go.
够了 我得再提醒你们一下
Again. More of this.
你可以亲这个混蛋一辈子
You get to kiss this jackhole for the rest of your life.
这个周末他是我的
This weekend, he's mine.
- 真是个混蛋 - 别找脱衣舞娘跟他上床
- Such a dick. - Don't let him bang any strippers.
什么?
What?
棕榈泉没有脱衣舞娘
There are no strippers in Palm Springs.
应该说棕榈泉没有一流的脱衣舞娘
Well, there's no decent strippers in Palm Springs, all right.
我带他到球场之后
Once I get him out on the course,
他脑袋里就只会想五号铁杆 艾美
the only thing he's gonna be banging is five irons, Ames.
好吧
Okay.
- 到了饭店后我再打电话给你 - 小心安全
- I'll call you from the hotel. - Be safe.
好的
All right.
- 要吃早餐吗? - 不用了 太早了吧
- A little breakfast? - No. I'm good. It's a little early.
- 你也不应该 - 这真的没什么
- Even for you. - This is nothing, man.
再过几小时 会有超辣的脱衣舞娘
In a couple of hours, you are gonna be doing blow
让你乐翻天
off some hot stripper's ass.
你说棕榈泉没有一流的脱衣舞娘
You said there were no good strippers in Palm Springs.
的确是没有
There aren't.
我们不是去棕榈泉 对吧?
We're not going to Palm Springs, are we?
(米高梅饭店)
(蔚蓝海岸)
天啊
Holy shit.
这是怎么一回事?
What the fuck is this?
安卡
Anka.
快醒一醒
Get up!
安卡
Anka!
嘿 你们到底是谁?
Hey! Who the fuck are you guys?
你们想做什么?
What the fuck you doing?
你们干嘛把我们关起来?
What the fuck you want with us?
安卡
Anka!
嘿
Hey!
有种来找我
Come to me!
大混蛋 别碰她
You motherfuckers, don't touch her! Aah! Aah!
别碰她
Don't touch her!
有种来找我
Come to me!
有种来找我 混蛋
Come to me, motherfuckers!
你们是谁? 你们
Who are you? Where...?
你们要带她去哪里?
Where the fuck are you taking her?
我不想死
Aah! I don't wanna die!
安卡 我会去救你的
Anka! I'm gonna come for you!
放手
Let go!
不
No!
安卡
Anka!
安卡 我会去救你的
Anka, I'm gonna come for you!
你们都死定了
All you motherfuckers are gonna die!
不!
No!
(精英酒店)
- 你还好吧? - 你的腿没事吧?
- What's up? - How's the leg?
- 没事 - 卡特
- It's okay. - Carter.
- 你好吗? 迈克 - 我很高兴你来了
- How are you, Mike? - I'm glad you made it.
我很高兴能来到这里
Good to be here.
- 你好吗? 谢谢你赶过来 - 我是绝不会错过的
- How you doing? Thanks for coming. - Wouldn't miss it.
我们不是为你来到这里的 这才是我们的目标
We're not here for you. We're here for this.
振动一下吧 好好用力跳一跳
Bounce it. Up and down, north to south.
这真的很棒吧? 美女在桌边为你服务
How great is this? Tits and ass at your table.
我可以看尽脱衣舞娘的表演
I could get all the stripper action I want,
当我老婆的面说我真的没去夜店玩 很天才吧
look my wife in the face and say I never went to the club. Genius.
- 坐吧 我们得好好玩一玩 - 好啊 酷啊
- Sit down. Let's do some damage. - Okay. Cool.
看吧 超级王牌 怎么样?
Ha-ha-ha! Look at that. Spade and neutered. What's up?
对 有些人为免费饮料而来 我可不是来输钱的
Yeah. Dude, some come for the free booze, I come not to lose.
付钱吧 混蛋
Pay me, motherfucker.
对 通杀到底 我赢了
Oh, yeah. Winner, winner, chicken dinner, bitches.
这整个地方像是在做实验
This whole place is a lab experiment.
看吧 没有窗户
Look. Look at it. There are no windows.
墙上没有时钟
There are no clocks on the walls.
他们灌入氧气 让你保持清醒
They pump oxygen in here to keep you awake.
提供免费饮料将你灌醉
They give you free booze to keep you drunk.
还要美女在你面前走来走去
They parade women in front of you on top of that.
目的是要赚你的钱 天啊 这个地方是邪恶的化身
It's all just to take your money. Man, this place is evil incarnate.
或许是吧 但能赢钱则是另当别论
Yeah, maybe so, but not when you're winning.
迈克 你似乎有点累了
Mikey, you're looking a little light over there.
我吗? 我很好 我担心的人是你
Oh, me? I'm golden. It's you I'm worried about.
天啊 别又来了
Oh, God. Don't start this shit.
等一下 什么?
Wait, what shit?
他的"不要"宣言 我听过各种版本
His ''don't do it'' speech. I've heard every version of it.
你会跟他说不要结婚 你不要他结婚
You're gonna tell him not to get married. You don't want him to.
- 可是你结婚了 你知道吧? - 对 我知道
- You're married, you know that, right? - Yeah. I know.
那跟下地狱差不多 卡特 真的
And it's a living hell, Carter. Seriously.
婚姻只是场马戏团游戏
Marriage is nothing but a three-ring circus.
订婚戒 婚戒 吃尽苦头 你会了解的
Engagement ring, wedding ring, suffering. You'll see.
对 但史考特可是不一样的
Yeah, but it's gonna be different for Scotty.
真的吗? 真有趣 怎么会?
Really? Interesting. How exactly?
因为他没有娶凶婆娘
Because he's not marrying a bitch.
看吧 没错 他娶到好女人
Oh, see, there it is. He comes in with a:
一星期后我要结婚 你跟你老婆
I am getting married in one week, and you and your lovely wife
- 一定要出席 - 我的漂亮胖老婆 我们会出席的
- are gonna be there. - My lovely fat wife. Yes, we will.
- 好吧 该走了 - 什么? 你在干嘛? 我手气真顺
- Okay, time to go. - What? What are you doing? I'm hot.
我知道 所以他们找人来煞风景 亚洲人会带来恶运
That's why they sent over the cooler. Asians are bad luck.
- 但你们做的烟火很不错 - 那是种族歧视冷笑话
- You make good firecrackers, though. - That is just some racist bullshit.
对不起 他不是有意的
I'm sorry, man. He did not mean that.
- 现在要做什么? - 我有太阳剧团的门票
- All right. So, what now? - Got Cirque du Soleil tickets.
你不只无能 你还是个娘娘腔
Oh, so you're not only disabled, you're also gay.
- 有时候是的 - 但那一点都不重要
- Sometimes. - But it's not gonna matter too much
因为史考特能大饱眼福
because Scotty is getting seriously eye fucked
看看吃角子老虎机旁边的美女 看到她们了吗?
by the girIs at the progressive slots. See them?
兄弟 她们超辣的 我敢说她们恨死自己的老爸了
Dude, they are hot. And I bet you they hate their fathers.
- 对 - 你在做什么?
- Yes. - What are you doing?
- 别闹了 - 我什么都没做
- Don't start. - I'm not doing anything.
贾斯汀 做你该做的事 过去吧
Justin, do your thing. Limp on over.
- 我对女人是很有一套的 - 能上床就是件好事
- Nothing wets a pussy like this hardware, huh? - Pity fuck is still a fuck.
没错
That's true.
你们好
Hey, guys.
- 我是坎卓 - 我是妮琪
- I'm Kendra. - I'm Nikki.
嗨 我是史考特 他们是卡特 迈克及贾斯汀
Hi. I'm Scott. This is Carter, Mike and Justin.
- 迈克 - 你们要一起玩吗?
- Mike. - So you girIs wanna join the party?
看起来场面有点冷清
Not much of a party.
- 我们才刚开始 - 我们有按摩浴缸
- We're just kind of getting started. - We have a Jacuzzi.
就在我们房里 如果你们想过来
It's in our room, if you guys wanted to head up there.
还真直接
Smooth.
你们有更棒的点子吗?
You guys have any better ideas?
我们知道一个地方 但它不在大道上
We know a place, but it's off the Strip.
对 它离大道非常远
Yeah, it's way off the Strip.
我不知道 或许来自郊区的乖男孩会受不了
I don't know, it might be too much for some nice boys from the suburbs.
有点古怪
It's a little freaky.
你们喜欢古怪吗?
Do you like freaky?
我们爱死古怪了 我们一直在追求古怪
We like freaky. We've always been into that sort of thing.
你呢?
What about you?
你喜欢古怪吗?
Do you like freaky?
对
Yeah.
当然喜欢
Yeah, sure.
(马戏团饭店赌场)
(坟场特价)
(廉价小镇)
听着 收音机这首歌
Hey, listen, on the radio here,
我喜欢这家伙 我有他的唱片
I love this guy. I have his records.
但你能不能小声点
But do you think you could turn it down a couple of notches
方便我们聊天?
so we can hear ourselves?
谢谢
Thank you.
你觉得那些女孩是专业人士吗?
Yeah. Do you think that those girIs are pros?
- 什么? 妓女? - 不 职业网球员
- What, hookers? - No, tennis pros.
谁在乎呢? 我只想跟她们炒饭
Who cares? I wanna poke them in their vaginas with Justin's crutch.
让她们知道我舌头的厉害 你了解我的意思吗?
Go check their oil with my tongue. Know what I mean?
没油了吗? 要加油吗?
A little low down there? You need a fill-up?
嘿 你的计费表没在动 兄弟
Hey, you know your meter's not working, man.
你们只要付我二十块就算扯平了
You high rollers pay me 20 bucks, I call it even.
- 你确定是这里吗? - 我想应该在那边
- You sure this is right? - I think that's it back there.
卫星定位系统显示就在这里
The GPS shows it should be right here.
你看到夜店了吗? 我没看到夜店
You see a club? I don't see a club.
我只看到培根工厂
All I see is a bacon factory.
你们在怕什么? 你们以为我会开车载你们到暗巷
What are you afraid of? Think I'm gonna drive you to the alley
让我的朋友偷走你们的钱 砍掉你们的头?
where my friends steal your money and cut your heads off?
好吧 该走了
Okay, time to go.
- 好吧 - 好吧
- All right. - Okay.
(大道上最美丽的女孩 不需要借口的相遇)
这里的确离大道很远
That is way off the Strip, all right.
- 你确定是这里吗? - 她给我们的住址的确是这里
- Are you sure this is it? - It's the address she gave us.
那些女孩说得对 这个地方是有点古怪
Those girIs were right. This place is pretty freaky.
你们有什么事吗?
What you want?
我们来参加派对
We're here for the party.
你们在名单上?
You on the list?
对 妮琪跟坎卓邀请我们过来
Yeah. Nikki and Kendra sent us?
所以你们已经说好了?
So you're that deal?
那是什么意思?
What does that mean?
我是说你们会玩得很开心
lt means you're gonna have a nice time.
进来吧 就是这里
Come on in. Down the hall.
天啊 这个地方感觉超恐怖的
Dude, this place feeIs fucked.
我想我们该离开
I think we should go.
- 什么? 去看太阳剧团? - 没错
- What, go check out Cirque du Soleil? - Sure.
原来你的确是个女的
Your vagina's hanging out.
- 什么? - 对
- What? - Yeah.
- 那怎么会跑出来? - 第二次了
- How did that get out? - Second time.
天啊
My goodness.
我们到了 或许该看的我们都看过了
Well, we're here. Might as well see what it's all about.
"或许该看的我们都看过了" 兄弟 我们哪里都不去
''Might as well see what it's all about.'' Dude, we're not going anywhere.
该死 是我的手机
Oh, fuck. That's me.
- 该死 老兄 - 是艾美
- Fuck, dude. - It's Amy.
或许你该接电话
You probably wanna take that.
- 你们算是已经结婚了 - 你猜我会怎么做
- You're practically married. - Guess what I do.
一离开我老婆身边 我会关手机
When I'm away from my wife, I turn off my phone.
让她无法打电话或传简讯给我
She can't call, can't text,
没办法逼我拍照证明我在哪里 因为她超没有安全感的
can't make me send a photo of where I'm at because she's insecure.
- 所以你的婚姻跌入谷底 - 她胖了三十磅 所以
- That's why your marriage sucks. - She put on 30 pounds, so...
艾美 嘿
Amy, hey.
你说你到了饭店后会打电话给我
You said you would call when you got to the hotel.
我知道 对不起
I know, I'm sorry.
听着 我们在外面 所以我得挂电话了
Um, look, we're just walking in somewhere, so I'm... I gotta go.
今晚回旅馆后我再打电话给你
So I'll call you when I get back to the hotel tonight?
- 史考特 - 什么?
- Scott. - Yeah?
我该担心你吗?
Should I be worried about you?
不
No.
请不要这样
Please don't do this.
你不必担心 好吗?
You have nothing to worry about, okay?
我爱你
I love you.
好吧
Okay.
我爱你
I love you.
伙计们?
Guys?
真爱开玩笑
Very funny.
哈啰?
Hello?
搞什么? 你在做什么?
What the fuck? What are you doing?
住手 我无法呼吸
Stop it! I can't fucking breathe!
你要带我去哪里?
Where the fuck are you taking me?
放开我
Ugh! Let me go!
搞什么?
What the fuck?
这个单身汉派对超棒的
Now, that's a bachelor party.
你们这些混蛋
Ah! You fuckers!
大混蛋
Ah! You assholes!
我要杀了你们
I'm gonna kill you. I'm gonna kill you.
- 这是你的计划吗? - 我不知道
- Are you in on it? - I had no idea.
史考特
Scott! Scott! Scott!
她们不穿上衣服 真的
They won't put their clothes on. They just won't do it.
你在生气吗?
Are you mad?
或许吧
Maybe.
你们设计我
You guys set me up pretty good.
他们付钱要我们那么做
Hey, it's what they paid us to do.
你是?
So you're a...?
现在大家是怎么称呼你们的?
What do they call you now?
这星期的说法是伴游
Oh, this week, ''escorts.''
你失望吗?
Are you disappointed?
不
No.
很好
Good.
我们走吧
Let's go.
去哪里?
Where?
香槟室
The champagne room.
你们会害我惹上大麻烦的
You are gonna get me in so much trouble.
嘿 我是安琪拉
Hey, I'm Angela.
嘿
Hey.
我是贾斯汀
I'm, uh... I'm Justin.
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 我得去找我朋友 - 没问题
- Gotta get back to my friend. - Sure.
亲爱的 你知道吗? 这玩意会硬上一整晚
Just so you know, darling, this thing stays hard all night.
谁惹毛她了?
Who lit the fuse on her tampon?
真好笑
Tampon.
你朋友有什么毛病?
What is wrong with your friend?
他的毛病可多了
A lot.
她配不上你
You're too sweet for her.
你何不待在这里呢?
So why don't you stay here?
我要你等我
I want you to wait for me
因为我不知道你朋友要闹多久 好吗?
because I don't know how long your friend's gonna be, okay?
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
我忍不住了
I just came in my pants.
她不是我老婆
That's not my wife.
别告诉任何人 帮我保密
Shh. Don't tell anyone. Keep a secret.
对
Yeah. Oh.
不 我们可以
No. No, no. Can we...? Can we just...?
慢慢来
Slow down, slow down, slow down.
慢慢来是件好事
Slow is cool.
- 我们能在这里待一小时 - 对
- We've got the room for an hour. - Yeah.
不
No, no. Um...
不 我想或许我们可以只聊聊天
No. I'm just thinking maybe we could just talk.
- 聊天? - 对
- Talk? - Yeah.
对
Yeah. Yeah.
譬如你是拉斯维加斯人吗?
Like, um, are you from Vegas?
你想聊这个?
Is that what you wanna talk about?
不 我只是
No, no. It's just that, um...
No. It's just that, uh...
这是你的第一次?
Oh. Oh. Is...? Is this your first time?
不 我
No. I'm...
我快结婚了
I'm getting married.
不是今晚
Not tonight.
不 不是今晚
Not tonight. No, not tonight.
- 拜托 坎卓 - 等一下
- Please, Kendra. Kendra. - Wait.
放轻松 好吗?
Just relax, okay?
没有人会知道
Nobody's gonna know anything.
对 我知道
Yeah. I know, I know.
不 听着 去年我出轨过
No, but look... Look. Look, I was... I was unfaithful last year.
我未婚妻知道后 我差点失去她
All right, my fiancee found out and I almost lost her.
好吧 我知道那听起来很逊 真的 但我只是
All right, I realize how fucking lame this sounds, I do, but I just...
我告诉自己我不想再那么做了
I told myself that I wasn't gonna be that guy anymore.
嘿 我了解
Hey, I get it.
没问题 什么事都不会发生
It's cool. Nothing has to happen.
我们只是一起消磨时光
We can just hang out.
至少 待在这里
At least, here.
再喝一杯
Have another drink.
史考特 我刚知道谁杀了肯尼迪 你想知道吗?
Scotty. I just found out who killed JFK. You wanna know?
你还穿着衣服 你动作太慢了 混蛋
You still have your clothes on. You are slow, you little bitch.
怎么了?
What's up?
- 有人在我们的房间吐了 所以 - 有人吐了?
- Somebody threw up in our room so... - Somebody?
对
Yeah.
- 对 就是你 - 你无法保密
- Yeah, you did. - Hey, you can't keep a secret.
闭上嘴巴 张开腿
Close your mouth, open your legs. Close your mouth, open your legs. Ha-ha-ha.
- 你没事吧? - 不
- Are you okay? - No.
不 我需要呼吸新鲜空气
No. I need to get some air.
好吧
Okay.
呼吸新鲜空气是件好事 喝一点水
Air is good. Air is good. Get some H2O.
不 喝点水 你在做什么?
No, that's water. Hey. What are you doing?
- 太棒了 - 你很辣 但我要你离开
- Great. - You're hot, but I need you to leave.
你比她辣多了 嗨 妮琪
You're hotter. Hi, Nikki.
印地五百
Indy 500.
再来一次
Ah! One more, one more.
开门
Open up!
快点 有人在吗?
Come on. Is anybody in there?
拜托
Please!
快开门
Open the fucking door.
准新郎终于醒了吗?
Bachelor boy finally woke up, huh?
对 我想他是尿在裤子里才醒的
Yeah. I think the warm piss in his pants did it.
我们以为你死了
We thought you were dead.
喝到烂醉
Just dead drunk.
天啊
Ugh. God.
我本来要背你上床
You know, I would have carried you to bed,
但你太重了 我有条腿受伤 所以
but you're fucking huge and I've got a gimpy leg, so...
我只记得我吐了 我被关在夜店外面
Last thing I remember, I was throwing up and got locked out of the club.
你怎么回来的? 我们回来时你已经在房里
How did you get back here? You were here when we got in.
那个计费表坏掉的计程车司机
The cabbie. The cabbie with the broken meter.
- 你有上她吗? - 没有 但她很可爱
- Oh. Did you at least get laid? - No. But she was a cutie.
那就真的惹毛我了
That pisses me off because
因为我付钱要那个妓女跟你上床 事先预付全额费用
I paid that whore good money to rock your world. In advance.
迈克在哪里? 他又吐昏在浴缸里了?
Where's Mike? Did he pass out in the tub covered in his puke again?
或许是吧 他不在这里 他跟那个叫妮琪的女孩回家了
Yeah, probably. But not here. He went home with that, uh, Nikki girl.
他一直没出现
He hasn't resurfaced.
你们有打电话给他吗?
Did you try calling him?
兄弟 他的手机没开
Dude, his phone's in the sex dead zone.
他出门就不开手机了 记得吗?
He's miles from home. Remember?
回凤凰城后他才会开手机
It's not gonna be on until we get back to Phoenix.
- 我是迈克 - 语音信箱
- You've reached Mike. - Voice mail.
- 我在拉斯维加斯 别烦我 - 迈克 我是史考特
- I'm in Vegas. Leave me alone! - Hey, Mikey, it's Scott.
打开手机 兄弟 我们在找你
Turn your phone on, man. We're looking for you.
我不会太担心迈克 他知道我们搭几点的飞机
I wouldn't worry too much about Mike. He knows what time our flight is.
拉斯维加斯就是这样 我说过这里太邪恶了
It's the spell of Vegas, man. Like I said, it is pure evil.
看起来迈克好好地享受了你的单身派对
Looks like Mikey was getting the bachelor party you were supposed to.
对
Yeah.
这是怎么一回事?
What the fuck is this?
你们在香槟里加了什么?
What the fuck did you guys put in that champagne?
味道臭死了
It's got a nasty aftertaste.
我知道我跟美女炒饭 这是怎么一回事?
I know I ate some fucking pussy. What is this?
好吧 我懂了 史考特 现在轮到你整我了
All right, I get it. I got you, Scott. Now you got me. Ha, ha.
快点 各位 搞什么?
Come on, guys. What the fuck?
- 该死 - 对
- Shit. - Yeah.
- 你的麻烦大了 - 你是谁?
- You are in the shit. - Who the fuck are you?
- 你在做什么? - 你觉得呢?
- What are you doing? - What does it look like?
- 我不想死在这里 - 谁说我们会死呢?
- I'm not gonna die in here. - Who said anything about dying?
- 放马过来吧 混蛋 - 发生了什么事?
- Come to me, motherfucker! - What is going on?
来吧 混蛋
Come on, you motherfucker.
他要对他做什么?
Argh! What is he doing to him?
天啊 我的老天爷
Oh, my God! Oh, my fucking God!
离我远一点
Get the fuck away from me!
史考特 贾斯汀 发生了什么事?
Scott! Justin! What the fuck is going on?
那家伙是个大混蛋
There's our snaky motherfucker!
我的天啊 离我
Oh, my fucking God. Get the...
- 我喜欢看他们打架 - 对
- I like when they fight. - Yeah.
下三滥
Fucking son of a fucking bitch!
放开我
Get the fuck off of me!
滚开
Fucking piece of shit!
这是什么病态笑话吗? 搞什么?
Is this a fucking joke? What the fuck?
去你的
Fuck you!
拜托 我什么都没做 这是个错误
Please. I didn't do anything. This is a mistake.
各位 拜托
Guys, please!
我是迈克·马洛伊 来自亚利桑纳州 放了我
My name is Mike Malloy from Arizona. Let me go.
闭嘴 拿出男子汉的模样
Shut your mouth. Take it like a man.
- 王八蛋 - 该死
- Fucking asshole. - Fucking Jes...
放我离开这里 你们到底是谁?
Let me the fuck out of here. Who the fuck are you?
你们到底是谁? 放开我
Who the fuck are you? Get the fuck off of me!
不
No, no! Aah!
这太糟糕了
This is fucking bad.
拜托 求求你们
Please. Plea... Fucking please.
搞什么? 你们要做什么?
What the fuck? What the fuck are you doing?
- 这是在开玩笑吗? - 对
- Is this a fucking joke? - Oh, yeah.
笑点是杀人凶手
And the punch line is a killer.
我朋友有钱 我们有钱 我们能付你们钱
My friends have money. We have money. We can pay you.
- 我们能付你们钱 - 有人已经付钱订下你了
- We can pay you. - You've already been paid for.
他在胡说什么? 什么?
What the fuck is he talking about? What?
你说有人订了我是什么意思? 这到底是怎么一回事?
What do you mean ''paid for''? What the fuck is going on?
这些人是谁?
Who the fuck are these people?
不
No!
(开始)
(恶运大轮盘)
(现有资产)
(健康程度良好 结婚五年 有两个孩子 被囚禁一天)
(要求/恳求)
(以家人为借口 二赔一)
你们到底是谁?
Who the fuck are you people?
你们要做什么?
What are you doing?
天啊 你们要做什么?
Oh, my God. What the fuck are you doing?
不 离我远一点
No, no. Get the fuck away from me. Get the fuck...
不 住手
No, stop.
住手 你们要做什么?
Stop. What the fuck are you doing?
住手
Stop.
(选择工具 电钻 十赔一)
该死
Oh, fuck.
不 你们要做什么?
No. What the fuck are you doing?
拜托 别让我
Please, don't let me...
求求你
Please.
求求你 住手
Please, stop.
住手
Stop! Stop!
Stop.
你到底有什么毛病?
What is wrong with you?
这是个误会
This is a fucking mistake!
拜托 住手 求求你不要
Please, stop. Please don't. Please.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
拜托
Please. Please.
我有太太 还有女儿跟儿子 他们分别是六岁跟四岁
I have a wife. I have a daughter, a son. They're 6 and 4.
以家人为借口求饶
Begging for family.
1分58秒 下注时间是两分钟
One minute, 58 seconds. The over-under was two minutes.
恭喜二号 五号及七号玩家
Congratulations to players two, five and seven.
她在胡说什么? 这是怎么一回事?
What the fuck is she talking about? What the fuck is going on?
我不懂
I don't understand!
这是怎么一回事?
What the fuck is this?
这一定是在开玩笑 不
This has to be a fucking joke. No!
不 求求你 不要
No, please, don't.
救救我 拜托
Help me, please.
迈克 我们还在找你
Hey, Mike, we're still looking for you.
我们开始担心了 回电话给我们
We're starting to freak out a little bit. Call us back.
- 或许我们该打电话给他老婆 - 听起来是个好点子
- Maybe we should call his wife. - That sounds like a very good idea.
"你看到迈克了吗? 昨晚我们丢下他离开派对现场"
''Have you seen Mike? We left him at a party last night
"他跟专业伴游在一起 他失踪了" 那是个好点子
with a professional escort and he disappeared.'' Good idea.
你觉得该怎么办?
What do you suggest?
或许他整晚没睡跟那个女孩胡搞 给他几小时的时间
He was probably up all night dicking that girl. Give him a couple of hours.
- 我们只是担心他 - 我不担心
- We're just worried about him. - Well, I'm not.
我是说看看我们四周
I mean, look around, huh?
我们四周全是美女 饥渴的家庭主妇
Everywhere you look, there are coeds and miIfs
还有寂寞的熟女 我是说我们该怎么办?
and cougars, you know? What are we gonna do?
- 去找他? 去哪里找? - 你在哪里找到那些女孩的?
- Look for him? Where? - Where did you find those girIs?
这里是拉斯维加斯 那一点都不难
It's Vegas. It's not hard.
你有跟伴游公司联络吗?
Was it some kind of service you called?
对 那是免费召妓专线 兄弟
Yeah, it was 1-800-WHORES, man.
我知道该怎么找到他
I know how to find him.
怎么找?
How?
我完全忘了 那个叫妮琪的女孩 她有给我名片
I totally forgot. That girl, Nikki, she gave me her card.
- 那是她的电子邮件信箱 - 我们得知道她的住址
- That's her e-mail address. - We need a street address.
不 这叫做网路追踪
Yeah. No, it's called cyber stalking.
我是这方面的高手
I'm pretty good at it.
嘿 妮琪 我是贾斯汀
Hey, Nikki, it's Justin,
昨晚拿着拐杖的帅哥
the guy with the crutch from last night.
我们在找我们的朋友 迈克 我们想问你知不知道他在哪里
We're looking for our friend. We're wondering if you know where he is.
请回我电话 谢谢
Please call me back. Thank you.
(香格里拉)
她真的住在拖车营地里
She definitely lives in a trailer park.
这是经典拉斯维加斯童话故事
This is a classic Vegas fucking fairy tale.
(香格里拉拖车营地)
- 几号? - W17
- What number is it? - Uh, W17.
- 在哪里? - 我不知道 卡特
- And where is that? - You know, I don't know, Carter.
我的手机没有白人妓女追踪程式
I don't have a white-trash locator on my phone.
在哪里? 真的在这里吗?
Where is it? Is it one of these?
我想还要再往前走
I think it's further up.
快到了吗?
Are we getting warmer?
- 是这间吗? - 对
- Is this the one? - Yeah.
听着 我想应该没有人在
Look, I don't think anybody's here.
哈啰?
Hello?
妮琪? 迈克?
Nikki? Mike?
不要
No. Mm-mm.
交给你了
Your show, man.
这是个烂主意
This is definitely a bad idea.
好吧
Okay.
- 你要一起来吗? - 不
- Are you coming? - Uh, no.
我想我得待在这里把风
I'll stay out here and keep watch, I guess.
天啊 这里好臭
God, it fucking reeks in here.
迈克?
Mike?
哈啰?
Hello?
天啊
Jesus.
你觉得他来过这里吗?
Does it look like he's been here?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想这解释为什么会有那些皮带
I guess it would explain all these strap-ons, though.
他应该离开这里了
He's obviously not here anymore.
我们快走吧
Let's get the fuck out of here.
那是什么声音?
What the hell was that?
贾斯汀
Justin.
天啊 趴下
Motherfuckers, get down!
- 通通给我跪下 - 我是史考特
- All of you, on your fucking knees now! - It's me, Scott.
我知道你是谁 你来这里做什么?
I know who you are. What are you doing here?
- 我们得跟妮琪谈一谈 - 所以你闯进她家
- We need to talk to Nikki. - So you broke into her house.
我想这只是拖车
I think this is actually a trailer.
闭嘴
Shut up!
好吧 冷静点
Okay, okay! Chill, chill!
别惹我们 你们为什么要找妮琪?
Don't fuck with us. Why are you looking for Nikki?
我们的朋友迈克昨晚没回饭店
Our friend Mike never came home last night.
我们离开前看到她跟他在一起
She was the last one we saw him with.
所以你以为他跟她回家
And you think that he just shacked up with her.
他是个完美男子 所以她必须带他回家
He's such an all-star lay, she had to take him home.
坎卓 听着 他没回我们电话 我们不知道发生了什么事
Kendra, look, he wouldn't call us back. We don't know what's going on.
这一定是个骗局 目的要骗光我们所有的钱
This is obviously a scam to get more money out of us.
你们要多少钱? 你呢? 大毒虫
How much do you want? What about you, meth mouth?
卡特 闭嘴
Carter, shut up!
听着 我们很抱歉自己闯进来 我们只是要跟她谈一谈
Look, we're sorry that we broke in. We just wanna talk to her,
- 问她知不知道迈克在哪里 - 你就是不懂 对吧?
- see what she knows about Mike. - You don't get it, do you?
我没办法问她
I can't ask her.
昨晚妮琪没回家
Nikki didn't come home last night.
风骚妓女
Tacky hooker.
太明显了
Too on-the-nose.
这样子好多了
Much better.
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
搞定
Get it done.
你想做什么?
What the fuck are you doing?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我在装可爱 跟你一样
Nice and sweet, like you.
什么?
Wh...?
救命啊
Help.
Help!
来吧 小美人
Come, mama.
救救我
Help me!
你拿那个做什么?
What are you doing with that?
不
No!
拜托 救命啊
Please. Help!
不
No. No.
你拿那个做什么?
What are you gonna do with that?
你想做什么?
What are you doing?
你要做什么?
What are you gonna do?
住手
Stop it!
我怎么知道你朋友没有伤害她?
How do I know your friend didn't hurt her?
因为我了解迈克 他不会伤害任何人
Because I know Mike. He wouldn't hurt anybody.
你知道我在这里学会什么吗?
You know what this town taught me?
没有人了解任何人
Nobody knows anybody.
在拉斯维加斯发生的事 就留在拉斯维加斯 对吧?
What happens in Vegas stays in Vegas, right?
总是会有个笨蛋
There's always that one son of a bitch
不了解这只是闹着玩的
who doesn't realize that this is all for show.
这不是真的
It's not real.
我一直都那么说
I've been saying that all along.
我们该如何找到他?
Um, how are we gonna find them?
我们得回到那家夜店 从头开始 追踪他们去了哪里
We're gonna go back to the club. Start at the beginning, retrace their steps.
- 不 我想我们该报警 - 不
- No. I think we should call the cops. - No.
每天在大道都有人失踪
People disappear off the Strip every night.
除非已经失踪一星期 不然警察是不会受理的
Police don't consider it a missing person till they've been gone a week.
听着 我们得找到他们
Look, we're gonna find them.
在这里没有"我们"
There's no ''we'' here.
我要去找我朋友
I just wanna find my friend.
你还是很辣
You're still fucking hot.
你死了还是很性感
You are dead fucking sexy.
该死
Oh, shit.
讨厌的小混蛋
Nasty little bitch.
这才是真的深喉咙
Say ''deep throat.''
那真的很棒 宝贝
That's good. That's really good, babe.
拍得不错 你觉得呢?
That's nice work. What do you think?
你不认为吗? 对 我也是
Hm? Don't you think? Yeah, me too.
再见
I'll see you.
各位
Guys, guys. Hey.
- 迈克传简讯给我 - 他说什么?
- I got a text from Mike. - What is he saying?
他说"抱歉闹失踪 我昏睡了一整天"
Uh, he says, ''Sorry to disappear on you. Crashed all day.''
- 他在哪里? - 妮琪在哪里?
- Where is he? - Where's Nikki?
等一下 我正要问他
Hold on, I'm asking.
你在哪里?
Where are you?
"我跟妮琪在一起 她在睡觉"
Ah. ''I'm with Nikki. She's sleeping.
"电池快没电了"
Battery dying.''
看吧
Mm. Check it out.
天啊 妮琪 你做了什么?
God, Nikki, what did you do?
等一下
Hey, wait.
"到这里跟我碰面 九号房 快一点"
''Meet me here. Room 9, ASAP.''
- 你知道那在哪里吗? - 费利蒙区
- Do you know where that is? - Fremont district.
好吧 我们得去扁死他
Okay, well, let's go kick his ass.
我要杀了他
I'm gonna fucking kill him.
(费利蒙)
你要来吗? 兄弟
Are you coming, gimpy?
我想保留体力参加残奥会
I think I'm gonna save myself for the Special Olympics.
我的腿快痛死了
My leg's killing me.
去找那个混蛋 然后我们就离开这里
Go get that asshole and let's get out of here.
(旅舍)
迈克
Hey, Mikey.
迈克 你在里面吗?
Mike, are you in there or what?
迈克?
Mikey?
妮琪?
Nikki?
至少我们知道他们来过这里 这是妮琪的皮包
Well, at least we know they were here. This is Nikki's purse.
他到底在搞什么?
What the hell is he up to?
这是他的手机
Here's his phone.
还有一张字条
And a note.
"各位 我们出去了 喝瓶啤酒放轻松"
''Guys, we stepped out. Have a beer and chill.''
至少我们知道他的礼貌还在
At least we know he hasn't lost his manners.
迈克
Hey, Mikey?
- 我们该在这里等他们吗? - 如果他们不会回来呢?
- So should we just wait here for them? - What if they don't come back?
抱歉事情变得一团糟
I'm sorry this all got so fucked up.
我很想跟你聊 可是我
As much as l'd love to have a moment, I'm just...
该死
Oh, fuck.
搞什么? 快走
What the fuck? Go, go.
不
No!
搞什么?
Whoa. What the fuck?
对不起 我
I'm sorry, man. l, uh...
- 你是贾斯汀吗? - 你吓死我了
- You Justin? - You scared the shit out of me.
我知道 对不起 但你朋友迈克在找你
I know. I'm really sorry about that, but Mike is looking for you.
- 他不在里面? - 他在街上的酒吧里
- He's not in there? - He's at a bar right down the street.
醉到走不动 他要我来找你
Too drunk to walk. He asked me to come get you.
好吧 真的吗?
Okay. He did?
对
Yeah. Yeah.
- 好吧 我打电话问他 - 好啊
- Okay, well, let me call him. - Cool.
- 还有一件事 - 什么? 该死
- Oh, one more thing. - What...? Ow! Oh, fuck!
我想你觉得那样很好玩 对吧?
Bet you thought that was fucking hilarious, didn't you?
听着 你们弄错了
Look, you motherfuckers are making a mistake!
你们弄错了 你们知道的 对吧?
Huh? You're making a fucking mistake! You know that, don't you?
你们不知道自己在做什么
You have no fucking idea what you're doing!
这是个天大的误会
Big fucking mistake!
- 他们都那么说 - 去死吧 人渣
- That's what they all say. - Suck my dick, you faggot.
我们到底在哪里?
Where the fuck are we?
是谁把我们关起来的?
Who's doing this to us?
很快你们就会见到他们
You're gonna meet them soon enough.
轮到你时 他们会来接你
When it's your turn, they'll come for you.
过来 你们这些大混蛋
Come here, you motherfuckers!
嘿
Hey! Hey!
讨厌的大混蛋
Fucking tough guys!
过来
Come over here!
安卡在哪里?
Where is Anka?
我不知道发生了什么事 不
I don't know what's going on. I don't... Hey, no! No!
- 不 - 该死 贾斯汀
- No. - Shit! Justin, Justin! Justin!
为什么他们要这样对我?
Why are they doing this to me?
发生了什么事?
What is going on here?
你们要带他去哪里?
Where are you taking him?
他是你的朋友?
That was your friend?
他是我的朋友 你又是谁?
That was my friend. Who are you?
那么你该跟他说再见了
You should've said goodbye to him, then.
嘿
Hey! Hey!
大混蛋 站住
Hey, you motherfucker, stop.
站住 过来
Stop. Come here.
- 你得排队 朋友 - 对 现在轮到我了
- Wait your turn, ese. - Yeah, it's my fucking turn right now.
那是怎么一回事?
What is that?
该死 你怎么不早说?
Shit, why didn't you say something?
来吧 快点 我们走
Come on. Hurry up, let's go.
- 退后 - 不
- Back up. - No.
卡特 发生了什么事? 那是怎么一回事?
Carter, what the fuck is going on? What is that all about?
这是名流猎杀俱乐部
It's Elite Hunting Club.
那是什么意思?
What the fuck does that mean?
这是会员专属权利
lt means members only.
你在胡说什么? 你要去哪里?
What are you talking about? Where are you going?
你要去哪里?
Where the fuck are you going?
你不能把我丢在这里
You can't leave me in here!
卡特!
Carter!
帮麦穆林先生送威士忌跟可乐过来
Get Mr. McMullin his Jack and Coke.
我不需要可乐
You can hold the Coke.
抱歉造成你的不便
Accept my apologies for any inconvenience.
不便? 你是那么说的吗?
Inconvenience? That's what you call that?
那些家伙 要把我当成一块肉般地拖走
Those guys were gonna drag me away like a piece of meat.
你感觉一定很特别
lt must have been a unique sensation for you.
我很高兴看到你很喜欢这工作
I'm glad to see you're enjoying this.
我们是专业人士
We are professionals.
我们绑架不会被想念的人 是有原因的
There's a reason we kidnap people who won't be missed.
你的特别要求引发了一些问题
Your special request has caused more than a few inconveniences.
我并不是有意的
That was never my intention.
你知道的 我是好客户
You know that. I'm a good client.
顶级客户
Top-tier client.
所以我一开始就很乐意配合
Which is why I entertained the idea in the first place.
我们得说双方都有错
Well, let's just agree that mistakes were made on both sides.
你觉得如何?
How do we move on?
女孩们可以补足额外的支出
The females will make up for the added expense.
其他人呢?
And the others?
你的朋友?
Your friends?
附带损失吗?
Collateral damage.
你有问题吗?
Do you have a problem with that?
如果你有问题 我可以打电话回总公司
If you do, I could call the home office.
他们不喜欢听到有问题
They don't like to hear about problems.
他们一直都是他的朋友 跟我不熟
They were always more his friends than mine.
所以我们没问题了?
So are we good?
干杯
Drink up.
(恶运大轮盘)
没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
他挨了九箭才断气
That was a total of nine arrows until termination.
恭喜五号及十一号玩家
Congratulations to players five and 11.
好戏上场
Showtime.
我要给那个大混蛋一个惊喜
I have big surprise for that cattle prod motherfucker.
他们会对她做什么?
What the fuck they doing to her?
他们带走我的女人
They took my woman.
他们带走我的安卡
They took my Anka.
这些大混蛋
These fucking people.
天知道他们对她做了什么
Who knows what they're doing to her?
她是我的生命
She was my life.
她是我的一切
She was my everything.
下星期我就要结婚了
I'm getting married next week.
至少你没在上星期结婚
Well, at least you didn't get married last week.
为什么?
And why is that?
不然你的女人现在已经是寡妇
Because your woman would be a widow now.
走吧 大帅哥
Let's go, pretty boy.
去你的
Fuck you.
那不是要求
Oh, that wasn't a request.
好吧
Okay!
史考特
Scott!
好吧
Okay, okay!
你们要带他去哪里?
Where the fuck are you taking him?
该死
Fuck.
来吧 大帅哥 只不过是一件外套
Come on, pretty boy. It's just a fucking jacket.
好吧
All right, all right, all right.
那件西装帅呆了
That's a nice tux.
不用还了 好好享受你的蜜月
Don't bother returning it. Enjoy your honeymoon.
欢迎会员光临
Welcome, members,
名流猎杀俱乐部主秀 特别杀戮游戏
to the Elite Hunting Club's main event, a very special kill.
好好享受节目
Enjoy the show.
(主秀)
- 别起来 没关系的 - 什么?
- Don't get up. It's fine. - What?
这是怎么一回事?
What is this?
这是怎么一回事? 卡特
What is this, Carter?
这个吗? 这是件超便宜的西装
This? This is actually a really fucking cheap tuxedo.
我特别为参加婚礼订做的
I have this very special custom job I was gonna wear to the wedding.
好吧
Okay.
我想现在我得穿着它参加你的葬礼了
I guess now I'll wear it to your funeral.
你在胡说什么?
What are you saying?
我以为他们办不到 但他们真的很厉害 记得这个吗?
Ho, ho, ho. I didn't think they'd be able to find it, but they did. Recognize these?
这真的很棒
This is really great.
你知道这是什么?
Do you know what these are?
那是超贵的德国菜刀
Those are the very expensive German kitchen knives
艾美指定的 布鲁明戴尔百货公司礼品
that Amy registered for at Bloomie's.
我很高兴他们准备了这个
I'm glad they're here
因为我用了类似这样的刀子
because I actually used a knife very much like this one
在澳门的夜店杀了一个女孩
to kill a girl at the club in Macau.
我活生生地剥下她的皮 那花了我六小时的时间
I skinned her alive. lt took me six hours.
- 你是哪门子的变态? - 我一直遇到的问题
- What kind of sick fuck are you? - But the problem that I keep running into
就是我的冲动不再
is that the rush just isn't there anymore.
我需要提振一下士气 我得杀死我关心的人
I needed to up the ante a bit. I needed to kill someone who mattered.
你怎么能逃得过? 你无法让我凭空消失
How are you gonna get away with it? You can't just make me disappear!
- 所以我付钱雇用这些人 - 什么?
- That's what I pay these people for. - What?
你要他们杀了你的朋友? 迈克跟贾斯汀在哪里?
What, to kill your fucking friends? Where are Mike and Justin?
- 你对他们做了什么? - 那真的是个误会
- What did you do with them? - That was actually a mistake.
那真的是个误会
That was a legitimate mistake.
迈克不幸地出现在不对的地方
That Mike was in the wrong place at exactly the right time.
而贾斯汀
And Justin...
那个可怜的混蛋 他不该落得那样的下场
The poor bastard. He didn't deserve it.
什么? 我活该落得这样的下场?
What, I deserve this?
为什么我活该落得这样的下场?
Why do I deserve this?
因为你拥有我要的东西
Because you got what I want.
艾美
Amy.
这跟艾美有关?
This is all about Amy?
我以为她逮到你劈腿时
I thought when she found out that you cheated on her
她会立刻离开你
she would leave you right away.
是你跟她说的
You told her.
是他跟她说的 大混蛋
You told her. You fucking...
她发现后一定会很崩溃
Oh, she is going to be devastated when she finds out.
你这个大变态
You sick fuck.
没关系 我会陪在她身边安慰她
But that's okay, I will be right there next to her to console her.
你这个大变态
You sick fuck.
- 你这个大变态 - 你觉得我得等多久
- You sick fuck! - And how long do you think it'll be
- 才能跟她上床? - 你这个大变态
- before I'm fucking her? - You sick fuck!
在你的床上
In your own goddamn bed.
别碰她 我会杀了你
Don't you touch her! I'll fucking kill you! I will fucking kill you.
你是哪门子的怪胎? 你这样对待自己的朋友?
What kind of man are you, huh? You do this to your fucking friends?
如果跟女人有关
When it comes to pussy,
我没有朋友
I have no friends.
你们要看表演吗?
You motherfuckers want a show?
- 我会让你们看表演 - 来吧
- I'll give you a fucking show. - Go ahead.
耶!
Yeah!
放了他
Let him go.
耶!
Yeah!
你们这些混蛋要看表演吗?
You motherfuckers want a show, huh?
我会让你们看表演
I'll give you a fucking show!
庄家必胜
The house always wins.
蜜月还没有结束 名流猎杀俱乐部会员们
The honeymoon isn't quite over yet, Elite Hunting Club members.
谁要下注新郎会被杀死?
Now, who wants to bid on killing the groom?
快放我出去 大混蛋
Get me the fuck out of here, you motherfuckers!
你们这些变态
You sick fucks!
来吧 放马过来 混蛋
Come on! Come to me, you motherfucker.
- 闭嘴 不然我会杀了你 - 放马过来
- Shut your mouth or I'll fuck you up! - Come to me.
- 轮到我了 - 大混蛋
- My turn now! - You motherfucker!
快给我
Give me that!
我超爽的
Oh, I'm so fucking happy.
你死定了 硬汉 这次轮到你了
You die, tough guy. It's your turn.
去死吧 混蛋 人渣
Die, motherfucker! Die, you piece of shit!
你这个大混蛋
You motherfucker!
去死吧
You fucking die.
我整死你了
Now I fuck your mother, okay?
该死
Fuck!
不
No!
去死吧 混蛋
Die, motherfucker!
看我的 混蛋
Take that, you fucking bitch!
来吧 大混蛋
Come on, motherfuckers!
重覆 两名囚犯逃脱
I repeat, we have two escaped prisoners on the loose.
好的
Okay.
老板 有两个人逃了
Sir. Sir, we have two on the loose.
- 叫警卫包围他们 - 是的 老板
- Have security round them up. - Yes, sir.
启动警报
Sound the alarm.
(危险 高压电)
天啊
Oh, my God.
我的老天爷
Jesus Christ.
天啊
Oh, God.
拜托
Oh, please. Please, please, please.
快点
Come on. Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
该死
Fuck!
- 那个混蛋 - 该死
- That mother... - Fucking shit!
该死
Shit!
快点
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
好 天啊 好 拜托
Oh, yes. Yes. Oh, God, please.
喔 天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God.
拜托
Please, please, please.
天啊 拜托
Oh, God, please.
警局总机 请问有什么事需要协助?
911 operator, what is your emergency?
我需要帮忙 他们在杀人
Yes, I need help. They're killing people.
你在哪里? 先生
What is your location, sir?
听着 我不知道我在哪里
Look, I don't know where I am.
- 没关系 先生 - 等一下
- That's okay, sir. - Oh, wait, wait.
- 请等一下 - 别挂线 保持冷静
- Please wait. - Stay on the line. Stay calm.
- 他们杀了我的朋友 - 杀了你的朋友
- They've killed my friends. - Killed your friends.
快点 他们会杀了我
Hurry. They're gonna kill me.
保持冷静 先生 别挂线
Remain calm, sir. Stay on the line.
我看到死人了
I see dead people.
我们查出发话地点了
We've got a point of location.
警察会立刻赶过去
The police are on their way.
该死
Fuck!
各位朋友们 请坐
My friends, please, keep your seats.
我们只是暂时断电
We are experiencing a temporary power interruption.
为了安全
As a safety precaution,
我们会护送各位上车
you will be escorted to your vehicles.
对 大帅哥报警了
Yeah. Tennessee tuxedo called the cops.
行动失败
We've been compromised.
好了 我们得离开
That's it, we're shutting down.
杀死囚犯?
Kill the prisoners?
把他们都杀了
Kill them all.
不能留下人证
No witnesses.
救救我 拜托
Help me, please. Please, help.
拜托 不要
Please, don't! Please!
天啊
Oh, God.
- 史考特 - 钥匙
- Scott. Scott. - Keys.
- 天啊 好了 - 快救我出去
- Oh, God. Okay. - Get me out.
- 快点 - 可恶
- Hurry. - Fuck!
快点
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
- 该死 - 该死
- Fuck! - Shit!
想离开这里只有一条出路 混蛋
Only one way out of here, motherfucker.
(EHC大楼 已启动炸弹)
(引爆时间)
干嘛急着离开呢?
Why the hurry, huh?
- 这里快爆炸了 - 是吗?
- The place is gonna blow. - Yeah?
该死
Fuck.
喔 天啊
Oh, Jesus.
该死
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
好吧
Okay.
去你的
Fuck you!
去死吧
Die!
去你的
Fuck you.
不 等一下
No! Wait!
你这个大混蛋
You motherfucker!
大混蛋 给我回来
You motherfucker, come here! Come... Wa...
不
No!
(引爆时间)
该死
Fuck!
我不敢相信他死了
I can't believe he's gone.
我只是 会发生这些事
I just... I feel like none of this would have happened
都是因为我带他去拉斯维加斯的原故
if I hadn't take him to Vegas.
快别那么说
Don't talk like that.
至少你还活着
Hell, at least, you survived.
没事了
It's okay.
尽管哭吧
You can cry.
卡特?
Carter?
什么事?
Yeah?
今晚我不想独处
I don't wanna be alone tonight.
你不必独处 艾美
You don't have to be, Amy.
我就在这里
I'm right here.
我哪里都不会去
I'm not going anywhere.
我得喝一杯
I need a drink.
- 你要喝一杯吗? - 好
- Would you like a drink? - Yeah.
我想喝一杯 好
I would love a drink. Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
- 需要我帮你吗? - 不
- Oh, can I help you with that? - Oh, no.
我可以的
I got it.
问题是
Problem is...
他还活着
he's alive.
我们何不完成我的单身派对呢?
What do you say we finish that bachelor party?
艾美 拜托你救救我
Amy, please help me.
庄家必胜
The house always wins.